Guide to the William Heyen Papers YCAL MSS 352
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
William Heyen papers
1915-2022
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Heyen, William, 1940-
YCAL MSS 352
955
77.89 Linear Feet (114 boxes)
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by William Heyen in the course of his activities as a poet and editor, and primarily documents Heyen's literary career from 1995 to 2009. Material includes correspondence with poets and writers, writings by Heyen and others, bound copies of Heyen's journals dating from 1965 to 1994, original journals dating from 1994 to 2006, notebooks, printed material, and other papers.
General note
This finding aid describes a collection that has been acquired by the library in discrete segments over time. The narrative sections of the finding aid provide information about the content and context of the collection. The Collection Contents section provides a general description and in some instances a box or folder listing of the various acquisitions of the collection. The Processing Notes section provides information about the way and extent to which the library has processed this collection. The Arrangement section provides information about how material within this collection is organized and tips on how to locate material across various acquisitions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from William Heyen on various funds, 2005-2023.
March 2011 Acquisition: Purchased from Clouds Hill Books on the Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 17 (electronic documents): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies available. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 76-77 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 78 and 114 (computer media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Associated Materials
William Heyen Papers Relating to William B. Ewert (YCAL MSS 235). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
William Heyen Papers (MC 71). Milne Special Collections, University of New Hampshire Library.
William Heyen (b. 1940)
William Heyen is an American poet and editor. He was born in Brooklyn, New York in 1940, and educated at the State University of New York at Brockton and Ohio University. He taught American literature and creative writing at SUNY Brockport for over thirty years before his retirement in 2000.
His books of poetry include: Erika: Poems of the Holocaust (1984), Crazy Horse in Stillness (1996), Pig Notes and Dumb Music (1998), Diana, Charles, and the Queen (1998), Shoah Train (2003), The Confessions of Doc Williams (2006), and A Poetics of Hiroshima (2008). He edited the collection of poetry September 11, 2001: American Writers Respond (2002).
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by William Heyen in the course of his activities as a poet and editor, and primarily documents Heyen's literary career from 1995 to 2009. Material includes correspondence with poets and writers, writings by Heyen and others, bound copies of Heyen's journals dating from 1965 to 1994, original journals dating from 1994 to 2006, notebooks, printed material, computer and audiovisual media, and other papers.
Writings by Heyen include typed and manuscript drafts of poems that appeared in Crazy Horse in Stillness (1996), Shoah Train (2003), and A Poetics of Hiroshima (2008), among other works; books annotated with manuscript drafts of poems and notes; and galley proofs of early published works, including Noise in the Trees (1974), Swastika Poems (1977), Long Island Light (1979), that were returned to Heyen when Vanguard Press was sold to Random House. Also included are correspondence and manuscripts relating to September 11, 2001: American Writers Respond (2002), edited by Heyen; correspondence, manuscripts, and art work stemming from planned collaboration between Heyen and the artist Robert E. Marx; correspondence with Joyce Carol Oates; and materials related to collaborations with June Prager and Douglas Knehans.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into nine groupings: I. February 2005 Acquisition, 1970-2003. II. May 2006 Acquisition, circa 1950-2006. III. August 2006 Acquisition, 1984-2005. IV. January 2010 Acquisition, 1961-2009. V. March 2011 Acquisition, 1979-2010. VI. October 2015 Acquisition, 1915-2015. VII. June 2021 Acquisition, circa 2006 December. VIII. August 2022 Acquisition, 2018 - 2020. IX. February 2023 Acquisition, 1937 - 2022.
Material within this collection has been organized by acquisition reflecting the fact that the collection has been acquired in increments over time.
Researchers should note that material within each acquisition overlaps with and/or relates to material found in other acquisitions. For instance, correspondence and writings can be found in all four groupings. In order to locate all relevant material within this collection, researchers will need to consult each acquisition described in the Collection Contents section.
Researchers should also note that similar material can be arranged differently in each acquisition, depending on how the material was organized when it was received by the library.
TypeCollection
https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&09bea0a1-0af0-409c-b937-e27d60c3ca21
American literature -- 20th Century; American literature -- 21st century; American poetry -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 21st century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Authors, American -- 21st century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Electronic documents; Poets; Heyen, William, 1940-; Knehans, Douglas; Marx, Robert E. (Robert Ernst), 1925-; Oates, Joyce Carol, 1938-; Prager, June
- February 2005 Acquisition, 1970-2003; 322483; (17 boxes)
  General note
  Formerly classed as Uncat MSS 747.
  Arrangement
  Arranged into two series: Correspondence and Other Papers, and Writings.
  Scope and Contents
  This portion of the collection consists of correspondence, writings, electronic files, printed ephemera, and other papers by or relating to William Heyen and his writing, including material related to September 11, 2001: American Writers Respond (2002).
  TypeCollection
  https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e2ec48b4-20e2-4463-a725-d2b32a8a4287
  - Correspondence and Other Papers, 1981-2003; 322568
    Correspondence is largely unsorted.
    This series contains emails, letters, notes, some writings and printed material.
    - Tyler-Bennett, Deborah, 322617 (Box 1)
    - Tagliabue, John, 322616 (Box 1)
    - Morgan, Robert, 322615 (Box 1)
    - Various correspondence, 1999-2003; 322614; 3 Folders (Box 1)
    - Jordan, Barbara, 1998-2002; 322613 (Box 1)
    - Hewitt, Geof, 322612 (Box 1)
    - Doubrago, Sharon, 2000; 322611 (Box 1)
    - Various correspondence, 2001 January-October; 322610; 2 Folders (Box 1)
    - Wisner, Carol, Louis Phillips and Joan Michelson, 2000-2001; 322609 (Box 1)
    - Various correspondence, 1988-1989; 1998-2002; 322608; 14 Folders (Box 1)
    - Schneider, Dan and Jessica, 2001; 322607 (Box 1)
    - Various correspondence, 2001-2002; 322606 (Box 1)
    - Ewart, William B., 1998-2001; 322605 (Box 1)
    - Various correspondence, 2001-2003; 322604 (Box 2)
    - Romania, 1999-2000; 322603 (Box 2)
    - Various correspondence, 1981; 1997-2003; 322602; 21 Folders (Box 2)
    - Confrancesco, Joan, 2002; 322601 (Box 2)
    - Various correspondence, 2000-2003; 322600; 3 Folders (Box 2)
    - Gaffney, Larry, 2003; 322599 (Box 2)
    - Various correspondence, 2001; 322598 (Box 2)
    - Michael Broomfield list, 1983-1987; 322597 (Box 2)
    - Various correspondence, 2001; 322596 (Box 3)
    - Various poems, typescript, 322595 (Box 3)
    - Various correspondence, 1988-2001; 322594 (Box 3)
    - Poems, 322593 (Box 3)
    - "Gilbert and Garbo In Love", by Christopher Conlon, corrected typescript, 322592 (Box 3)
    - The Writer's Forum, circa 1987; 322591 (Box 3)
    - The Spine of the World, typescript, 322590 (Box 3)
    - Cadillac Battleship by Duane Esposito, typescript, 322589 (Box 3)
    - The Urban Stampede, by F.D. Reeves, typescript, 2002; 322588 (Box 3)
    - Between Frog and Water, corrected typescript, 322587 (Box 3)
    - "Fixed Stars", "The Novelist" and "On Shredding", typescripts, 322586 (Box 3)
    - Various writings, including Pipeline, 322585 (Box 3)
    - My Life with Joyce Carol Oates, typescript, 322584 (Box 3)
    - The Scar, 322583 (Box 3)
    - First Meeting, 322582 (Box 3)
    - Montague, various poems, 322581 (Box 3)
    - Silver Maple, 322580 (Box 3)
    - Occasions, 322579 (Box 3)
    - Bob Good eulogy, 322578 (Box 3)
    - Respects, 322577 (Box 3)
    - Dumb Beautiful Munsters, 322576 (Box 3)
    - The Window, 322575 (Box 3)
    - Various Heyen writings, 322574 (Box 3)
    - Distance and various writings, 322573 (Box 3)
    - Various correspondence, 2001-2002; 322572; 4 Folders (Box 3)
    - Printed ephemera, 322571; 3 Folders (Box 3)
    - Certificates, 322570
    - Books, 322569 (Box 3)
  - Writings, 1990-2002; 322490
    Arranged into three subseries: Crazy Horse in Stillness, Annotated Books; Other Poetry Drafts; and September 11, 2001: American Writers Respond.
    - Crazy Horse in Stillness, annotated books, 322539; (27 volumes)
      Arranged alphabetically by author.
      Includes books used by William Heyen for inspiration while writing poems for Crazy Horse in Stillness (1996). Heyen has written out drafts of poems on the flyleaves, margins and on the blank pages of the books. All books are heavily annotated.
      - Connell, Evan S. Son of the morning star: Custer and the Little Bighorn (1991), 322567 (Box 4)
        This book contains first drafts of several poems, including "Signals" and "Grass."
      - Crow Dog, Mary. Lakota Woman (1990), 322566 (Box 4)
        This book contains first drafts of several poems, including "Rattle," "Patriot," and "Mother."
      - Custer, Elizabeth B., 322562
        William Heyen read Elizabeth Custer's books for background information while working on Crazy Horse in Stillness. Following the Guidon (1890) and Tenting on the Plains (1895), contain first drafts of poems, including "Echoes," "Decades Later Libbie Remembers the Toads," and "George to Libbie, 1869."
        - Boots and Saddles (1885), 322565 (Box 4)
        - Following the Guidon (1890), 322564 (Box 4)
        - Tenting on the Plains (1895), 322563 (Box 4)
      - DeBarthe, Joe. Life and adventures of Frank Grouard (1982), 322561 (Box 4)
        This book contains first drafts of about twenty poems, including "Reluctance," "Grouard: The Chickens," "Shadow Memory," "Association of Sensibility," "Geometry," Sitting Bull's Reply," "Fast," "Paunch," and "Ars Poetica."
      - Dodge, Richard Irving. Plains of North America and their inhabitants (1989), 322560 (Box 4)
        This book contains first drafts of about 25 poems, including "Rock Custer," "Snowbirds," "The Bear," "Wildcat," "Grasshopper Sperm," "Dream," "The White Disease," "Dodge on Deposition," "Earring," Savings Account," "Custer, Around a Civil War Campfire," and "Prospects."
      - Eastman, Charles A. Indian boyhood (1971), 322559 (Box 4)
        This book contains the first draft of one or two poems.
      - Frazier, Ian. Great Plains (1989), 322558 (Box 5)
        This book contains first drafts of several poems, including "Snuff," "Fusion," and "Looney Tunes."
      - Frost, Lawrence A. The Custer Album: A Pictorial Biography of General George A. Custer (1984), 322557 (Box 5)
        This book contains first drafts of two or three poems, including "Boots," "1869 Photograph," and "A.D."
      - Grant, Bruce. Concise encyclopedia of the American Indian (1989), 322556 (Box 5)
        This book contains the first draft of "Feathers."
      - Haines, Francis. Buffalo: The Story of American Bison and Their Hunters (1970), 322555 (Box 5)
        This book contains first drafts of about 10 poems, including "Here," "5th Avenue," "Wedding Food," "Iron Horse," "Modern Art," and "Super Collider."
      - Hook, Jason, 322552
        - American Indian Warrior Chiefs (1991), 322554 (Box 5)
          This book contains the first drafts of two poems, "The Hunt" and "Medicine."
        - Crazy Horse: Sacred Warrior of the Sioux (1989), 322553 (Box 5)
          This book contains the first drafts of three poems: "Crazy Horse Laughs," "Camera Obscura," and "Short Bull on Photographs of Crazy Horse."
      - Hyde, George E. Red Cloud's Folk (1957), 322551 (Box 5)
        This book contains the first drafts of a few poems, including "Verdi," "Cooper Union," and "After-Image."
      - Jones, Douglas C. Court martial of George Armstrong Custer (1976), 322550 (Box 5)
        This book contains the first drafts of several poems, including "The Paper It's Written On," "The Treaty," and "Blood & Sage."
      - Jones, Gene. Where The Wind Blew Free (1967), 322549 (Box 5)
        This book contains the first drafts of two to three poems, including "Surveyors" and "Heat."
      - Kinsley, D. A. Custer: Favor the Bold - A Soldier's Story (1992), 322548 (Box 5)
        This book contains the first drafts of approximately 15 to 20 poems, including "Hot Battle Cold Shower Custer," "The Keeping," "The Bear," "The American Civil War," "The Animal," "General Sherman to Libbie," "Custer Declines to Sit for a Marble Bust," and "Letter from the Black Hills."
      - Matthews, Anne. Where the Buffalo Roam (1992), 322547 (Box 6)
        This book contains first drafts of about 6 poems, including "Root Music," "Gene Calves," "The Closing," and "God Does Not Have a Plow."
      - Matthiessen, Peter. In the Spirit of Crazy Horse (1983), 322546 (Box 6)
        This book contains first drafts of several poems, including "Fuse" and "Awls." William Heyen has credited this book with spurring the Crazy Horse in Stillness poems.
      - Miller, David Humphreys. Custer's Fall: the Native American Side of the Story (1992), 322545 (Box 6)
        This book contains first drafts of several poems, including "Coffee," "Directions," and "Tom Custer."
      - Moeller, Bill and Jan. Crazy Horse: His Life, His Lands - A Photographic Biography (1987), 322544
        This book contains first drafts of poems, including "Horns," "In this Dimension," and "Wingdust."
      - Norris, Kathleen. Dakota: A Spiritual Geography (1993), 322543 (Box 7)
        This book contains first drafts of approximately a dozen poems, including "Shoals," "Timewarp," "Thought," "Evening Heart Angel Ascension," "Live Oaks," and "V."
      - Red Fox, Chief. The Memoirs of Chief Red Fox (1971), 322542 (Box 7)
        This book contains first drafts of a poems, including "Breasts" and "In 1905 Crazy Horse Visits the Steamship Nebraska."
      - Swann, Brian. Smoothing the Ground: Essays on Native American Oral Literature (1983), 322541 (Box 7)
        This book contains the first drafts of one poem, "Curly Watches a Storyteller, 1850."
      - Utley, Robert M. Lance and the Shield: the Life and Times of Sitting Bull (1993), 322540 (Box 7)
        This book contains the first drafts of about 10 poems, including "Oriole," "Attack on Fort Union," "Lakota Challenge...," "Government Policy, 1870," and "Custer Ozymandias."
    - Other Poetry Drafts, 1990-1998; 322521
      Arranged alphabetically by title of work. Notebooks are arranged as a group at the end of the subseries.
      - Crazy Horse in Stillness, 1995; 322538; 18 Folders (Box 8)
      - Custer minus Custer, 1995; 322537 (Box 9)
      - Diana, Charles & the Queen, 1997-1998; 322536; 3 Folders (Box 9)
      - Pig Notes & Dumb Music, 1997; 322535; 7 Folders (Box 9)
      - Poems, 1997; 322534 (Box 9)
      - Rope, undated; 322533; 4 Folders (Box 9)
      - Rope: poems, 322532; 3 Folders (Box 9)
      - Rope: poems of Crazy Horse & Custer; The river of electricity; The confessions of Doc Williams, 322531 (Box 9)
      - Rope/Tumbleweed/Waterhook, 322530; 2 Folders (Box 9)
      - Shoah Train: Poems, 322524
        - On an Injunction by Theodor Adorno: Holocaust, 322529; 2 Folders (Box 10)
        - Shoah Train: poems, 322528; 7 Folders (Box 10)
        - Shoah Train: poems, 322527; 3 Folders (Box 11)
        - This train: Holocaust poems, 322526 (Box 11)
        - Vic Holyfield's Dream, 322525; 2 Folders (Box 11)
      - Notebooks, 1990-1997; 322523; 5 Folders (Box 12)
      - Notebooks, 1990-1997; 322522; 6 Folders (Box 13)
    - September 11, 2001: American Writers Respond, 2001-2002; 322491
      This subseries consists of correspondence and manuscripts, relating to September 11, 2001: American Writers Respond (2002), edited by William Heyen. Included are several hundred letters and manuscripts compiled over the three-month period after September 11, 2001, in which the book took shape. Also included are rejected submissions and correspondence with authors who declined to be part of the project.
      - Sept 11 Correspondence, 2001; 322520 (Box 14)
      - Adi / Ai / Allman (Mairowitz) / Attenderfer / Antler / Appleman / Atkinson / Baker, 2001-2002; 322519 (Box 14)
      - A. Barnstone / W. Barnstone / Bedelman / Berry / Bizzaro, 2001; 322518 (Box 14)
      - Blomain / Bond / Bourne / Borenstein / Bornstein, 2001; 322517 (Box 14)
      - Brady / Budbill / Chappell / Cherry / Clemente / Clifton / Conlon, 2001-2002; 322516 (Box 14)
      - Day / A. Deming / R. Deming / DiMatteo / E. Dodd / W. Dodd / Doubiago, 2001; 322515 (Box 14)
      - Edelman / Elder / Falls / Foerster / T. Gallagher / Galvin / N. Gallagher / Garrigue / Giancola / Gioseffi, 2001-2002; 322514 (Box 14)
      - Glancy / Goedicke / Goldstein / Gonzalez / Griffin / Hahn / Hazo, 2001-2002; 322513 (Box 14)
      - Heyen, 2001-2002; 322512 (Box 14)
      - Heller / Hellus / Hewitt / Higgins / H.E. Hex / H. L. Hix / Hinton / Hogue / Holmes / Hoppenthaler, 2001-2002; 322511 (Box 14)
      - Irwin / Jarman / Johnson / Jong / Kennedy / Kingston / Kowit / Krapf / Kuhl, 2001-2002; 322510 (Box 14)
      - 9/11 Literary tribute, from the Mulberry Poets and Writers Journal, 2002; 322509 (Box 14)
      - H. Taylor / K. Taylor / Unger / Updike / Vas Dias / Vigrer / Watson / Waters / Weiss, 2001-2002; 322508 (Box 14)
      - Wilbur / John A Williams / Terry Tempest Williams / Wise / Zimmer, 2001; 322507 (Box 14)
      - Levan / Liman / LoLordo / Longenbach / Louis / Mariani / Mason / Masterson / Matthews, 2001-2002; 322506 (Box 14)
      - Mazzaro / Meels / Merwin / Mulls /Minty / Mooney / Monarmatico / Mozina / Nelson / Nye, 2001-2002; 322505 (Box 14)
      - Ogden / Ostriber / Pambey / Pesetsky / Pinsky / Plumly / Poniewaz, 2001-2002; 322504 (Box 14)
      - Ragain / Ray / Reed / Reeve / Pizzato / Robertson, 2001-2002; 322503 (Box 14)
      - Sanders / Scott / Sheck / Spires / St. John / A. Stone / R. Stone / Street / Stryk / Swann, 2001-2002; 322502 (Box 14)
      - Writers accepting, 322501 (Box 14)
      - Writers declining / unable / etc., 322500 (Box 14)
      - Publicity / Clippings / reviews, etc., 322499 (Box 14)
      - Tom Wall and Cathy Jewell, 322498 (Box 14)
      - New Yorker / Orion and other material (some used in Anthology), 322497 (Box 14)
      - Etruscan Press (Michael Valliant), 322496 (Box 14)
      - Rejected, 322495 (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 322494; 3 Folders (Box 14)
      - Etruscan Press (Michael Valliant), 2002; 322493 (Box 15)
      - In Hand and In Book - address cards, 322492; 6 Folders (Box 15)
  - Oversize, 1970-2003; 322486
    - Certificates (from Correspondence and Other Papers), 1970-2003; 322489 (Box 16)
    - Printed ephemera (from Correspondence and Other Papers), 1995, 2001, undated; 322488 (Box 16)
    - Moeller, Bill and Jan - Crazy Horse: His Life, His Lands - A Photographic Biography (1987) (from Writings), 322487 (Box 16)
  - Computer media, 322484
    https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d9e5d04f-c020-43d9-bc5c-3c83c74a8411
    - Book: Sept 11, 2001 American Writers Respond, 2005-ycal-0223-d-0001; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 17)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&96af6d91-81f2-4b5b-8e9a-c75339aa40d5
- May 2006 Acquisition, circa 1950-2006; 322320; (13 boxes)
  Formerly classed as Uncat MSS 868.
  Arranged into three series: Correspondence, Journals, and Writings.
  This portion of the collection consists of correspondence, writings, journals and printed material by or relating to William Heyen.
  - Correspondence, 1950-2000; 322408
    Arranged into two subseries: Family and General.
    - Family, 1950-1989; 322473
      - William Heyen to Hannelore Heyen (Greiner), 1959-1964; 322482; 9 Folders (Box 18)
      - Heyen, Hannelore (Greiner) to Drachowski, Irene and Robert, 1958; 322481 (Box 18)
      - Heyen, Hannelore (Greiner) to Drachowski, Irene and Robert, 1960-1962; 322480; 4 Folders (Box 18)
      - Heyen, Hannelore (Greiner) to Drachowski, Irene and Robert (Han's letters to her mother), 1963; 322479 (Box 18)
      - Heyen, William and Hannelore to Drachowski, Irene and Robert (letter from Germany to Hannalore's parents), 1971-1972; 322478; 2 Folders (Box 18)
      - Letters returned to Heyen for various reasons, circa 1950s; 322477 (Box 18)
      - Heyen, Mini and Henry to Heyen, William and Hannelore (letters from Heyen's parents), undated, circa 1975-1989; 322476 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous family correspondence: Henry & Janice, Ed & Cheryl, Alan, Werner, Barb, Wolf & Pat, Han's Mom, Han's Uncle Walter, several letters from Walter to Drachowski, Irene, etc., circa 1950-1960; 322475; 3 Folders (Box 19)
      - Heyen, Hannelore, political campaign poster "Hanny Heyen for Village Trustee", 322474
    - General, circa 1980-2000; 322409
      Bulk of correspondence is arranged into two alphabetical groupings by correspondent.
      - Silko, Leslie Marmon, 1995 Dec 29; 322472 (Box 19)
        Includes: Manuscript of "Gardens in the Dunes"
      - Sherman, Alexie and Silko, Leslie Marmon, 1995-1997; 322471 (Box 19)
        Includes: Bound collection of correspondence including some copies of replies from Heyen.
      - Letters to Liman, Claude, circa 1990-2000; 322470 (Box 19)
        "Letters to Claude Liman returned to me"
      - Louis, Adrian C., 322468 (Box 19)
      - Antler, 322467 (Box 20)
      - Bell, Madison Smart, 322466 (Box 20)
      - Bell, Marvin, 322465 (Box 20)
      - Blockeel, Dirk, 322464 (Box 20)
      - Booth, Martin, 322463 (Box 20)
      - Carruth, Hayden, 322462 (Box 20)
      - Claeson, Steve, 322461 (Box 20)
      - Dunn, Stephen, 322460 (Box 20)
      - Falk, Marcia, 322459 (Box 20)
      - Gallagher, Tess, 322458; 2 Folders (Box 20)
      - Garber, Zev, 322457 (Box 20)
      - Garret, George, 322456 (Box 20)
      - Hix, H.L., 322455 (Box 20)
      - Kaminsky, Ilya, 322454 (Box 20)
      - Katz, Eliot, 322453 (Box 20)
      - Kennedy, X.J., 322452 (Box 20)
      - Lee, Li Young, 322451 (Box 20)
      - Mangan, Kathy, 322450 (Box 20)
      - Mariani, Paul, 322449 (Box 20)
      - Matthews, Jack, 322448 (Box 20)
      - Merrill, Christopher, 322447 (Box 20)
      - Merwin, W. S., 322446 (Box 20)
      - Minty, Judith, 322445 (Box 20)
      - Oates, Joyce Carol (and Smith, Raymond), 322444 (Box 20)
      - Ozick, Cynthia, 322443 (Box 20)
      - Scott, Nathan A., 322442 (Box 20)
      - Smith, Dave, 322441 (Box 20)
      - Spires, Elizabeth, 322440 (Box 20)
      - Time Being Books, Timeless Press, 322439 (Box 20)
      - Waters, Michael, 322438 (Box 20)
      - Watson, David, 322437 (Box 20)